Concert for George is a music, documentary film directed by David Leland.
As a memorial to George Harrison on the first anniversary of his passing, The Concert for
George was held at the Royal Albert Hall in London on 29 November 2002 .
Organized by Harrison's widow, Olivia, and son, Dhani, and arranged
under the musical direction of Eric Clapton and Jeff Lynne.
A benefit for Harrison's Material World Charitable Foundation, the all-star
concert took place on the day of the first anniversary of his death.
Proceeds from the film also went to the Material World Charitable Foundation.
The film was shot using discreet cameras from over twelve locations.
Self, played by Joe Brown.
Self, played by Eric Clapton.
Self, played by Jools Holland.
Self, played by Sam Brown.
Self, played by Jeff Lynne.
Self, played by Paul McCartney.
Concert for George is a 2003 British documentary film directed by David Leland that covers the events of the Concert for
George, a tribute concert for George Harrison held at the Royal Albert Hall in London on 29 November 2002.
The film explores themes of concert, rock 'n'
roll, tribute, reunion, concert film.